If Sari hadn't slipped up, I wouldn't have known.
사리가 실수하지 않았다면, 몰랐을 겁니다.
All you do is attack me!
당신이 하는 일은 나를 공격하는 것뿐입니다!
Why don't you try to understand what I'm actually doing?
이해하려고 노력하지 그래? 내가 실제로 뭘 하고 있는 거지?
I'm just protecting my family's interests!
나는 단지 보호할 뿐입니다 내 가족의 이익을 위해!
And I am protecting the interests of the hotel!
그리고 나는 보호하고 있다 호텔의 이익을 위해!
If we are going to get a new investor
우리가 갈 경우 새로운 투자자를 확보하기 위해
or partner for Hotel 88, it should come from our side.
또는 Hotel 88의 파트너, 그것은 우리 쪽에서 나와야 합니다.
Yeah, that's wonderful news.
네, 정말 좋은 소식이네요.
I more than willing to help you with the hotel.
나는 당신을 기꺼이 도와주고 싶습니다. 호텔과 함께.
You're so mad at Martin,
마틴에게 너무 화났군요,
yet you've also talked to someone else.
아직도 얘기했잖아 다른 사람에게.
Luna, you know we're going to fight over this.
루나, 알지? 우리는 이 문제로 싸울 것입니다.
Hey! [BLOW LANDS] Who are you?!
여기요! [BLOW LANDS] 당신은 누구입니까?!
Your brother.
당신의 형제입니다.
I think he has something to do with my missing father.
내 생각엔 그 사람이 할 일이 있는 것 같아 실종된 아버지와 함께.
It's Sandro Soliman!
산드로 솔리만입니다!
What do you have to do with Sandro?
무엇을 해야 합니까? 산드로와 함께?
Don't ever mention that name in our home.
그 이름은 절대 언급하지 마세요 우리 집에서요.
I'll help you.
제가 도와드리겠습니다.
If I found out
내가 알았다면
you guys were the reason my Papa went missing,
너희들이 이유였어 내 아빠가 실종됐어,
I'll make you all pay!
내가 모두 대가를 치르게 해줄게!
[SARI] Why me?
[사리] 왜 나야?
You're close with Sir Martin, right?
당신은 가깝습니다 마틴 경과 함께죠?
[TONGUE CLICKS] Just tell Sir Martin yourself
[혀클릭] 마틴 경에게 직접 말해 보세요
that the guest's bracelet wasn't there
그 손님의 팔찌 거기 없었어
when you cleaned their room.
당신이 그들의 방을 청소했을 때.
[WAVES CRASHING]
[파도 충돌]
[MARTIN] Sari!
[마틴] 사리!
He's coming.
그가 온다.
Hey, don't leave me!
이봐, 날 떠나지 마!
Sari.
사리.
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[다가오는 발자국]
Sir, uh...
선생님, 어...
about the guest's bracelet,
손님의 팔찌에 대해
our housekeepers can't find it
우리 가정부들이 그걸 찾을 수 없어
in the areas you've asked them to check.
지역에서 당신은 그들에게 확인을 요청했습니다.
The guest said that's where they left it.
손님이 말했다. 그것이 그들이 떠난 곳입니다.
That means--
즉--
That they took it?
그들이 가져갔다고?
- Possible. - [GLOOMY MUSIC PLAYING]
- 가능한. - [우울한 음악 재생]
Sir, you know what, we shouldn't accuse anyone.
선생님, 그거 아시죠? 우리는 누구도 비난해서는 안 됩니다.
Hold on. Why are you the one reporting this to me?
기다리다. 왜 당신이 그 사람입니까? 나한테 이걸 보고한다고?
Sir, they are scared.
선생님, 저 사람들은 겁을 먹고 있어요.
[MARTIN SCOFFS]
[마틴 비웃음]
They shouldn't be
They shouldn't be
if they didn't do anything wrong.
그러면 안 돼
So tell them to check it again
만약 그들이 하지 않았다면 아무것도 잘못되었습니다.
because I'll deduct the cost of that bracelet
그러니 다시 확인하라고 말해줘
from their paycheck.
내가 공제할 테니까 그 팔찌 가격
Sir, let's not point fingers.
월급에서.
Maybe the guest just forgot where they placed it.
선생님, 손가락질하지 마세요.
Did I ask for your opinion? No, I didn't!
어쩌면 손님이 잊어버렸을 수도 있어요 그들이 그것을 어디에 두었는지.
So just shut up, Sari!
내가 당신의 의견을 물었나요? 아니요, 그렇지 않았습니다!
- [GLOOMY MUSIC CONTINUES] - [FOOTSTEPS RETREATING]
그러니까 그냥 닥쳐, 사리!
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
- [우울한 음악이 계속됨] - [후퇴하는 발자국]
[CUTLERY CLINKING]
[테마 음악 재생]
Jade, you don't have to hurry.
[칼이 딸깍거리는 소리]
Why didn't you tell me about the investment?
어서, 제이드. 말해봐, 뭐가 문제야?
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
왜 나한테 말하지 않았어? 투자에 대해?
Jade, I thought Luna was the one to tell you.
[침울한 음악 재생]
Edward.
제이드, 내 생각에는 루나가 너한테 말했잖아.
We're always together.
에드워드.
Every lunch and coffee break.
우리는 항상 함께 있어요.
And you didn't even care drop a hint.
매 점심시간과 커피 브레이크.
Jade, I just didn't want to get ahead of Luna.
그리고 넌 신경도 안 썼지 힌트를 던져라.
Hold on, why are you so pissed about it?
제이드, 난 그냥 원하지 않았어 루나보다 앞서려고.
What's the problem if we become investors?
잠깐만요 왜 그렇게 화났어?
What are your intentions anyway?
무엇이 문제인가? 우리가 투자자가 된다면?
To help you out, of course. That's all.
대체 당신의 의도는 무엇입니까?
Look, Jade.
물론 당신을 돕기 위해서죠. 그게 다야.
It's business, okay?
봐, 제이드.
And weren't you the one who said
그건 사업이니까, 알았지?
not everything's to be shared?
그리고
You don't tell me everything either.
모든 것이 공유되는 것은 아닌가요?
Yes, because you're not involved in it.
당신은 나에게 말하지 않습니다 모든 것.
Right. I'm not involved
응, 넌 아니니까 그것에 참여했습니다.
so I don't have the right to know, is that it?
오른쪽. 난 관련이 없어
Edward, this is not about you.
그래서 난 없어 알 권리, 그게 다야?
Okay.
에드워드, 이건 당신에 관한 것이 아닙니다.
[JADE] Okay.
좋아요.
- [CHAIR SQUEAKS] - Lunch is over.
[제이드] 알았어.
Bye.
- [의자가 삐걱거리는 소리] - 점심 식사가 끝났습니다.
[FOOTSTEPS RETREATING]
안녕.
[SCOFFS]
[후퇴하는 발자국]
[FOOTSTEPS]
[비웃음]
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[발자국]
[SARI BREATHING HEAVILY]
[사리가 훌쩍훌쩍]
I may just be your employee...
[사리의 거친 호흡]
...but you have no right to talk to me like that!
난 그냥 당신의 직원일 수도 있어요...
You're so harsh!
...하지만 당신에겐 권리가 없어요 나한테 그런 식으로 얘기하다니!
[SARI SCREAMS]
당신은 너무 가혹한!
- [SARI CRYING] - [FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[사리 비명]
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [사리가 울다] - [다가오는 발자국]
[SARI SNIFFLES, GROANS]
[부드러운 음악 재생]
Sir Leon, do you need anything?
[사리가 훌쩍이며 신음함]
[SARI SNIFFLES]
레온 경, 필요한 것이 있으신가요?
If you're going to cry, then let it all out...
[사리가 훌쩍훌쩍]
...instead of getting embarrassed in front of Martin.
울 것 같으면, 그럼 다 털어놔...
If you do, you know he'll just get angrier.
...받는 대신 마틴 앞에서 당황스러워요.
Sir Leon...
해보시면 아시겠지만 그는 단지 더 화를 낼 것입니다.
When I start crying, I might not stop.
레온 경...
You'll have a hard time calming me down from crying.
내가 울기 시작하면, 나는 멈추지 않을 수도 있습니다.
I really don't know
당신은 힘든 시간을 보낼 것입니다 울고 있는 나를 진정시키다.
why Martin chose you as his secretary
정말 모르겠어요
when you're the total opposite of him.
마틴이 당신을 선택한 이유 비서로
[GENTLE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[부드러운 음악이 계속됩니다]
Opposites attract, right?
반대가 끌리죠?
[LEON CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
[레온이 부드럽게 낄낄거린다]
See? You can lighten things up
보다? 상황을 밝게 할 수 있어요
even when Martin treats you harshly.
마틴이 치료할 때에도 당신은 가혹하게.
Sir Leon...
레온 경...
I'm sorry if...
미안해요...
I caused Miss Luna and Sir Martin to fight.
내가 미스루나를 일으켰지 그리고 마틴 경이 싸우러 갑니다.
Whether it was you or someone else...
당신이었는지 아니면 다른 사람...
Luna would still get angry.
루나는 여전히 화를 낼 것이다.
Don't be too harsh on yourself.
자신에게 너무 가혹하지 마십시오.
Thank you, Sir Leon.
고마워요, 레온 선생님.
They're right. You are kind.
그들이 옳습니다. 당신은 친절합니다.
Just do your job, Sari.
그냥 일이나 해라, 사리.
Everything will be okay.
모든 것이 괜찮을 것입니다.
Just don't give up on Martin.
마틴을 포기하지 마세요.
He needs you.
그는 당신이 필요합니다.
Oh. Sir.
오. 선생님.
- Your handkerchief. - Keep it.
- 손수건. - 그대로 두세요.
[GENTLE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[부드러운 음악이 계속됩니다]
I'm definitely not going to give up.
난 절대 안 갈 거야 포기하다.
I'd cry or vomit, but I won't give up!
울거나 토할 것 같았어요 하지만 난 포기하지 않을 거예요!
[EXHALES]
[숨을 내쉬다]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[날카롭게 숨을 내쉰다]
[LUNA] Just a quick meeting while there are no guests.
[루나] 그냥 잠깐의 만남 손님이 없는 동안.
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[다가오는 발자국]
Andy Arellano.
앤디 아렐라노.
I'm trying to get him as a partner of the hotel.
나는 그를 잡으려고 노력 중이야 호텔의 파트너로서.
Andy Arellano.
앤디 아렐라노.
The prominent businessman on Isla Kaluguran?
저명한 사업가 이슬라 칼루구란에?
Edward's dad?
에드워드의 아빠?
[LUNA] Yes.
[루나] 네.
He's willing to invest money in the hotel.
그는 기꺼이 호텔에 돈을 투자합니다.
We just need to sign.
서명만 하면 됩니다.
[MARTIN] But he's an investor, not a partner.
[마틴] 하지만 그는 투자자이고 파트너가 아닙니다.
Was that clear?
분명했나요?
He'll invest a lot of money in the hotel,
그 사람은 돈을 많이 투자할 거예요 호텔에서
why wouldn't he become a partner?
왜 그 사람은 안 되지 않을까? 파트너?
Being a partner is only for the inheritors.
파트너가 되는 것은 단지 상속자들을 위해서.
Did your father inherit the hotel to Andy Arellano?
아버지가 물려받았나요? 앤디 아렐라노에게 호텔을?
[LUNA] I thought you were thinking
[루나] 난 생각했어 넌 생각하고 있었어
of the hotel's best interest?
호텔의 가장 큰 관심사는 무엇입니까?
Why are you being so difficult with this partnership?
왜 이렇게 힘들어요? 이번 파트너십으로?
[LEON] Martin, the Arellanos have been
[레온] 마틴, Arellanos는
our family's friends for a long time.
우리 가족의 친구들 오랫동안.
Maybe we can amend the partnership
어쩌면 우리가 수정할 수도 있을 것 같아요 파트너십
to be able to accommodate him
그를 수용할 수 있도록
based on the terms that we agree on.
조건에 기초하여 우리가 동의하는 것입니다.
Amend the partnership?
파트너십을 수정하시겠습니까?
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[불길한 음악 재생]
Okay.
좋아요.
Then Uncle Ronald can be a partner, too.
그렇다면 로널드 삼촌은 파트너도요.
[MARTIN] Uncle Ronald has been
[마틴] 로널드 삼촌이
a long-time friend of the Madrigals,
오랜 친구 마드리갈의
like Andy with you.
당신과 함께 있는 앤디처럼요.
So, there's nothing wrong if he becomes our partner, right?
그렇다면 아무 문제가 없습니다 그 사람이 우리 파트너가 되는 거죠, 그렇죠?
But you said his decision wasn't final, right?
하지만 당신은 그의 결정을 말했지 최종은 아니었지, 그렇지?
But I can convince him.
하지만 나는 그를 설득할 수 있어요.
You know me, Leon.
당신은 나를 알고 있어요, 레온.
More investors, more money.
더 많은 투자자, 더 많은 돈.
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
[불길한 음악이 계속됨]
That sounds fair and good for the hotel.
공평한 것 같군요 그리고 호텔에 좋아요.
[LEON] So, that's it.
[레온] 그럼 그게 다야.
Hotel 88 will partner with Andy Arellano and Ronald Lucero.
호텔88이 파트너가 됩니다. 앤디 아렐라노와 로널드 루세로.
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
[불길한 음악이 계속됨]
[SARI] Ma'am, here are the towels, blankets,
[사리] 부인, 여기 있습니다 수건, 담요,
and pillowcases from your room.
그리고 방의 베갯잇.
They've already been washed,
이미 세탁됐어요,
and we've inspected them thoroughly.
그리고 우리는 그것들을 검사했습니다 철저하게.
The bracelet isn't there.
팔찌가 거기 없어요.
We've also vacuumed your entire room,
우리도 청소했어요 방 전체를
but we still couldn't find the bracelet.
하지만 우리는 아직 찾지 못했어요 팔찌.
Of course, it's already been passed
물론, 이미 통과되었습니다
to your staff's accomplices.
당신 직원의 공범자에게.
[SIGHS]
[한숨]
Ma'am, the only thing we haven't inspected yet
부인, 유일한 것은 아직 검사하지 않았어
is your bag.
네 가방이야.
I've already shown you my suitcase.
난 이미 보여줬어요 내 여행가방.
And you're still accusing me?
그런데 아직도 나를 비난하는 겁니까?
Ma'am, we haven't checked your personal bag yet.
부인, 아직 확인하지 않았습니다 아직 개인 가방이 없습니다.
Fine. Here!
괜찮은. 여기!
[OBJECTS CLATTERING]
[객체가 덜그럭거리는 소리]
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[생각에 잠긴 음악 재생]
Ma'am.
부인.
This is your bracelet, right?
이게 네 팔찌 맞지?
[RAPHIE] Madam! Your bracelet.
[래피] 부인! 당신의 팔찌.
- What a magic! - [CHUCKLES]
- 정말 마법이군요! - [웃음]
Ma'am, you really are forgetful.
부인, 정말 건망증이 심하시네요.
It was just in your bag.
그것은 단지 당신의 가방에 있었습니다.
I really checked this carefully. I didn't notice.
정말 꼼꼼히 확인했어요. 나는 눈치 채지 못했습니다.
Ah, to both of you, sorry, okay?
아, 두 사람 모두 미안해요, 알았죠?
- [SARI SIGHS] - So that's it?
- [사리의 한숨] - 그게 다야?
Just let it go.
그냥 놔두세요.
What's important is we proved there's no thief in this hotel.
중요한 것은 우리가 증명했다는 것입니다 이 호텔에는 도둑이 없어요.
Thank you, Sari.
고마워요, 사리.
You didn't give up on us.
당신은 우리를 포기하지 않았습니다.
I believe in the goodness of people.
나는 선함을 믿는다 사람들의.
So, I thank you!
그래서 감사합니다!
- Wow! - [APPLAUDING]
- 우와! - [박수]
Alright, alright! Sir Martin might see us.
알았어, 알았어! 마틴 경이 우리를 볼 수도 있어요.
Let's go.
갑시다.
[JADE CHUCKLES]
[제이드 웃음]
Sari's really something, right?
Sari는 정말 대단한 존재죠?
You know, I like her.
알다시피, 나는 그녀를 좋아합니다.
[CHUCKLING]
[웃음]
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[소프트 음악 재생]
Coffee update.
커피 업데이트.
Let's go.
갑시다.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[부드러운 음악이 계속됩니다]
Another coffee update?
또 다른 커피 업데이트?
They might start having palpitations.
그들은 시작할 수도 있습니다 심계항진이 있습니다.
[BOTTLES CLINKING]
[병이 딸깍거리는 소리]
Really?
정말?
[KIKO] Yeah.
[키코] 응.
The bracelet's been returned,
팔찌가 반환되었습니다.
she even managed to make the guest apologize
그녀는 심지어 성공했다 손님이 사과하게 하려면
to the two staff she accused.
그녀가 고발한 두 직원에게.
Your secretary's really something, isn't she?
당신 비서는 정말 뭔가요, 그렇죠?
Oh, looks like you didn't expect that.
아, 그런 것 같아 당신은 그것을 기대하지 않았습니다.
Yeah, even if you yell at her...
그래, 네가 그녀에게 소리를 지르더라도...
she still feels inspired to keep going.
그녀는 아직도 영감을 받은 것 같아 계속해서.
She even did better.
그녀는 심지어 더 잘했습니다.
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
[부드러운 음악 재생]
[BOTH GIGGLING]
[둘 다 낄낄거림]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[은밀한 잡담]
[GIO] Yo.
[지오] 요.
I know we still have an issue...
아직 문제가 있다는 걸 알아요...
with the investor, but can I go to the city for a while?
투자자와 함께, 하지만 내가 할 수 있을까? 잠시 도시에 갈까?
You're visiting your grandma?
할머니를 만나러 가시나요?
Hopefully.
바라건대.
So I can check on her personally.
그래서 확인할 수 있어요 그녀에게 개인적으로.
Go ahead.
계속하세요.
Just a few days anyway.
어쨌든 며칠이면 됩니다.
Just let me know if you need anything for her.
그냥 알려줘 그녀에게 필요한 것이 있다면.
Thanks, bro.
고마워요, 형제.
[GENTLE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[부드러운 음악이 계속됩니다]
Hi!
안녕!
- Wow! - Your iced coffee, Miss Jade.
- 우와! - 아이스커피요, 제이드 씨.
- Thank you, Raphie. - That's brewed from the heart.
- 고마워요, 라피. - 마음에서 우러나온 것입니다.
- [EDWARD] Wow. - Do you need anything?
- [에드워드] 와우. - 필요한 게 있나요?
Pancakes, appetizers? You name it, we have it.
팬케이크, 전채? 당신이 이름을 말하면 우리는 그것을 가지고 있습니다.
- It's okay. You made this? - It's okay. Thank you, Raphie.
- 괜찮아요. 당신이 이걸 만들었나요? - 괜찮아요. 고마워요, 라피.
- Yes. - This is good.
- 예. - 좋은데요.
- Thank you.
- 감사합니다.
- Thank you too. Enjoy! - Thank you, Raphie.
- 나도 고마워요. 즐기다! - 고마워요, 라피.
That was fast service.
빠른 서비스였습니다.
You said Sir Edward might be the hotel's new partner.
당신은 에드워드 경이 그럴 수도 있다고 말했어요 호텔의 새로운 파트너.
So they can see they're not making a mistake
그래서 그들은 그렇지 않다는 것을 알 수 있습니다 실수를 하고 있어
investing in Hotel 88, right?
호텔 88에 투자하는 거 맞죠?
Trying to impress him?
그에게 좋은 인상을 주려고 하시나요?
You should do that for all customers.
그렇게 해야 해 모든 고객을 위해.
Of course!
물론!
But Sir Edward is still different.
하지만 에드워드 경 여전히 다릅니다.
He's boss-level now.
이제 상사급이군요.
Like you!
당신처럼!
Are we on the same level?
우리는 같은 수준인가요?
- You own the hotel. - Mh-mm.
- 당신은 호텔을 소유하고 있습니다. - 음-음.
He's a partner.
그는 파트너입니다.
Well, that's kind of the same level.
글쎄요, 친절하네요 같은 수준의.
But he has more money than you, admit it.
하지만 그 사람은 돈이 더 많아 너보다 인정해라.
And also, no offense...
그리고 또한, 기분 나쁘게 하지 마세요...
I heard he studied at a business school in Singapore.
그 사람이 대학에서 공부했다고 들었어 싱가포르의 경영대학원.
Oh, so he can contribute tips to the hotel, right?
아, 그럼 그 사람이 기여할 수 있겠네요 호텔 팁 맞죠?
- Really? - Tsk. Mm-hmm.
- 정말? - 쯧쯧. 음-흠.
And I heard from a friend of a cousin
그리고 내가 들었던 건 사촌의 친구
who's a regular of mine and Monette
단골 누구야? 나와 모네트의
that when he got back from Singapore,
그 사람이 돌아왔을 때 싱가포르에서
he personally fixed up his hotel and managed it himself.
그는 개인적으로 호텔을 고쳤어요 그리고 스스로 관리했습니다.
That's why his guests suddenly increased.
그래서 그 손님이 갑자기 늘었습니다.
Amazing, right?
놀랍지 않나요?
Aside from being handsome and rich...
존재하는 것 외에 잘생기고 부자...
Wow! He's also good at business.
우와! 그 사람 사업도 잘해요.
He's pretty impressive, right?
그는 꽤 인상적이군요, 그렇죠?
Of course.
물론.
Oh.
오.
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
[부드러운 음악 재생]
[MONETTE] Raphie?
[모네뜨] 라피?
Can you check Room 201? They might have a concern.
201호를 확인해 주시겠어요? 그들은 우려할 수도 있습니다.
- Ah, excuse me. - Do it now.
- 아, 실례합니다. - 지금 하세요.
I'll leave you here for now. Alright!
지금은 여기 두고 가겠습니다. 괜찮은!
[GENTLE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[부드러운 음악이 계속됩니다]
[SARI] Oh! Hi, sir!
[사리] 아! 안녕하세요 선생님!
The front desk is over here. Come on in.
프런트 데스크는 이쪽이에요. 어서 들어오세요.
Ah.
아.
Now I get why they say it's great to stay here.
이제 왜 그들이 말하는지 알겠습니다. 여기 머무르는 것이 좋습니다.
Because guests are welcomed by someone like you.
손님을 맞이하기 때문에 당신 같은 사람에 의해.
[CHUCKLES]
[웃음]
It really is a wonderful place to stay.
정말 멋진 곳이네요 머물다.
The view is beautiful,
경치가 아름다워요
the amenities are excellent,
편의 시설이 훌륭해요,
and our staff are very friendly.
그리고 우리 직원들은 매우 친절합니다.
[GUEST] They're beautiful too.
[게스트] 그들도 아름다워요.
And...
그리고...
pleasing to the eye.
눈에 즐겁다.
[CHUCKLES AWKWARDLY]
[어색하게 웃는다]
Oh, sir, please don't say things like that to our staff.
아 선생님, 말하지 마세요 우리 직원들한테 그런 말을 해요.
You might get sued for harassment.
고소당할 수도 있어요 괴롭힘을 위해.
But with you, it's okay, right?
하지만 당신과 함께라면 괜찮겠죠?
Sir, would you like to check in?
선생님, 체크인하시겠습니까?
Ah, yes.
아, 그렇죠.
Please come in, sir.
들어오세요 선생님
Raphie will assist you.
라피가 도와드리겠습니다.
We can talk at the front desk.
우리는 얘기할 수 있어요 프론트 데스크에서.
We're so happy to have you here at Hotel 88.
우리는 당신이 있어서 정말 행복해요 여기 호텔 88에 있어요.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
[RAPHIE] Welcome to Hotel 88, sir!
[RAPHIE] 에 오신 것을 환영합니다 호텔 88 선생님!
The hotel that's witnessed secret crushes.
목격한 호텔 비밀 짝사랑.
Just kidding!
농담이에요!
The hotel that was once evicted is now making a comeback!
한때 쫓겨났던 호텔 지금 컴백 중이에요!
Do your real job.
진짜 일을 하세요.
Universe!
우주!
More patience, please!
좀 더 기다려주세요!
[SIGHS]
[한숨]
Isn't that too much?
너무 많은 것 아닌가?
Grandma's the only one who'll eat all that.
할머니는 하나뿐이야 그걸 누가 다 먹을까.
It's really good.
정말 좋아요.
Monette got them from her regular vendor.
모네트가 그걸 얻었어 그녀의 정규 공급 업체로부터.
She might like them.
그녀는 그것을 좋아할 수도 있습니다.
Tell her they're from us, okay?
그녀에게 그것들이 우리에게서 왔다고 말해주세요, 알았죠?
[GIO CHUCKLES]
[지오 웃음]
Hang on, can I ask you something?
잠깐만요, 뭐 좀 물어봐도 될까요?
Hm?
흠?
Have you ever had a girlfriend?
혹시 그런 적이 있나요? 여자친구?
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[생각에 잠긴 음악 재생]
What kind of question is that?
그것은 어떤 종류의 질문입니까?
I think you've had one already.
내 생각에 당신은 이미 하나를 가지고 있다고 생각합니다.
I'd actually be more surprised if you hadn't.
사실 내가 더 놀랐을 텐데 그렇지 않았다면.
So, have you had a girlfriend?
그럼 여자친구는 있었나요?
Are you being serious?
진심이에요?
Just answer the question.
질문에 답하면 됩니다.
No! There, happy?
아니요! 거기, 행복해요?
[MARTIN] What do you mean?
[마틴] 무슨 뜻인가요?
And why are you still here?
그런데 당신은 왜 아직도 여기에 있나요?
I thought you've left?
떠난 줄 알았는데?
I'm about to. Kiko's just being annoying.
나는 곧이다. 키코가 짜증나네요.
What is it?
그것은 무엇입니까?
I just asked him if he has a girlfriend.
방금 그 사람한테 물어봤는데 그에게 여자친구가 있다면.
He could've just answered instead of being defensive.
그 사람은 그냥 대답할 수도 있었어 대신 방어적인 태도를 취하십시오.
Why did you even ask him that?
왜 그 사람한테 그런 걸 물어봤나요?
No reason.
이유가 없습니다.
How about you? Do you have a girlfriend now?
당신은 어떤가요? 지금 여자친구 있어요?
Now? No.
지금? 아니요.
But I'm sure he's got a lot of exes.
하지만 난 그 사람이 그럴 거라고 확신해 많은 exe.
What's this really about, Kiko?
이게 정말 무슨 일이야, 키코?
Just say it.
그냥 말해보세요.
Are you courting someone?
당신은 누군가를 구애하고 있습니까?
Do people even still court these days?
사람들은 아직도 법정에 서나요? 요즘?
You don't court anymore?
이제 구애 안 하시나요?
Wait. Answer the question first.
기다리다. 먼저 질문에 대답하십시오.
There's someone I like.
내가 좋아하는 사람이 있어요.
- But... - [GIO] But what?
- 하지만... - [지오] 그런데 뭐요?
You don't want to pursue her?
그녀를 쫓고 싶지 않아요?
You just said courting isn't a thing anymore.
방금 구애한다고 말했잖아 더 이상 문제가 아닙니다.
For me, it depends on the girl.
나에게는 그 소녀에 따라 다릅니다.
But sometimes, if you really like someone,
하지만 때로는 누군가를 정말 좋아한다면
even if she's not into it, you'll still go for it.
그녀가 그 일에 관심이 없더라도 당신은 여전히 ​​그것을 갈 것입니다.
Wait. Are you asking because you don't know what to do?
기다리다. 때문에 묻는 건가요? 당신은 무엇을 해야할지 모르겠어요?
What if we're not a good match?
우리가 잘 맞지 않으면 어떡하지?
Ah. So you're insecure.
아. 그래서 당신은 안전하지 않습니다.
It's not like that.
그렇지 않습니다.
[GIO] Yeah, it is. You can't fool me, Kiko.
[지오] 그렇죠. 넌 날 속일 수 없어, 키코.
Why do you think you're not a good match?
왜 그렇게 생각하는가? 너랑 안 맞는데?
I don't know.
모르겠습니다.
It's like she's up here, and I'm down here.
마치 그녀가 여기 있는 것 같아 그리고 나는 여기 아래에 있어요.
There's so many things I can't give her.
너무 많은 것들이 있어요 나는 그녀에게 줄 수 없습니다.
She's out of my league.
그녀는 내 리그에서 벗어났습니다.
Oh, man. That's tough.
아, 이런. 힘든 일이다.
But once you start something, you have to stand by it.
하지만 일단 뭔가를 시작하면, 당신은 그것을 지켜야합니다.
Don't...
하지 마세요...
lead someone on.
누군가를 이끌어주세요.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[생각에 잠긴 음악이 계속됨]
I'll go now.
나는 지금 갈 것이다.
- Take care.
- 잘 지내세요.
Found you! Kiko!
당신을 찾았습니다! 키코!
Do we have a VIP guest?
VIP 손님이 있나요?
No, not really.
아니요, 그렇지 않습니다.
[STAFF] I'm done cleaning here, sir.
[직원] 여기 청소는 다 끝났어요, 선생님.
Ah, okay. Start on the other side.
아, 알았어. 시작 반대편에.
- I'll finish up here. - Okay, sir.
- 여기서 마치겠습니다. - 알겠습니다.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
[JADE] Why are you personally handling it yourself?
[제이드] 왜 그래? 개인적으로 직접 처리하시나요?
I'm just doing my assigned work, Jade.
난 그냥하고 있어요 내가 맡은 일은 제이드야.
Housekeeping. This is my job.
가정. 이것이 내 일이다.
[JADE] I know that, Kiko.
[JADE] 알아요, 키코.
I was just wondering if you're free,
그냥 궁금해서 그랬어 시간이 있으면
- maybe we could-- - I'm busy. Sorry.
- 아마도 우리는-- - 바빠요. 죄송합니다.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[침울한 음악 재생]
Kiko, are you okay?
키코, 괜찮아?
Of course. I just have a lot to do.
물론. 나는 할 일이 많다.
We don't want the new investor to think
우리는 원하지 않는다 생각해 볼 새로운 투자자
that the workers here are lazy.
여기 일하는 사람들이 게으른 것 같아요.
- But-- - Do you need anything else?
- 그런데-- - 더 필요한 게 있나요?
I need to help the staff.
직원을 도와야 해요.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[침울한 음악이 계속됨]
I'll go now.
나는 지금 갈 것이다.
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
[심호흡]
What's his problem?
그 사람의 문제는 무엇입니까?
This is a lot, dear!
이건 정말 많아요!
Look, I can't possibly finish all of this!
봐, 난 도저히 그럴 수가 없어 이것저것 다 끝내라!
I'll give some to Preska, okay?
내가 프레스카한테 좀 줄게, 알았지?
Do whatever you want, Grandma.
하고 싶은 대로 하세요, 할머니.
It's all yours anyway.
어쨌든 그것은 모두 당신 것입니다.
Kiko told me to tell you that they'd send some stuff too.
키코가 나한테 그걸 말하라고 했어 그들은 물건도 보낼 것입니다.
Your brother is so nice, isn't he?
형이 너무 착해요, 그렇지 않나요?
Even though I haven't seen him again.
난 그런 적 없는데도 그를 다시 봤어요.
But you know...
하지만 아시다시피...
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[침울한 음악 재생]
You forgot something that I really love.
잊어버린 게 있어요 내가 정말 좋아하는 것.
Grandma, I didn't buy you pork belly because I know that--
할머니, 저는 당신을 사지 않았어요 삼겹살 나도 그걸 알기 때문에--
I meant this!
내 말은 이런 뜻이었어!
I've missed my grandson's hug!
손자의 포옹이 그리웠어요!
- [GRANDMA SQUEALING] - I missed you too, Grandma.
- [할머니의 비명소리] - 나도 보고 싶었어요, 할머니.
Look!
바라보다!
Wow! Look at yourself.
우와! 너 자신을 봐.
Your complexion changed a bit.
안색이 조금 변했어요.
Huh?
뭐?
You look handsome right now.
당신 지금은 잘생겼어요.
Only now?
지금만?
You got more handsome!
더 멋있어지셨어요!
It seems the island's air suits you better!
섬의 공기인가 보다 너한테 더 잘 어울려!
It's also hot there, Grandma, but...
거기도 덥고, 할머니, 하지만...
the air there is different.
거기 공기가 달라요.
It's not polluted there.
거기는 오염되지 않았습니다.
- It feels different. - [GIO'S GRANDMA SQUEALS]
- 느낌이 달라요. - [GIO의 할머니가 비명을 지른다]
- "It feels different!" - [GIO HISSES]
- "느낌이 달라요!" - [지오 히스]
Maybe that happens when someone gives you a different feeling!
어쩌면 누군가가 그럴 때 일어날 수도 있습니다. 색다른 느낌을 줍니다!
Mom, you talk too much.
엄마, 말이 너무 많아요.
[DOOR OPENS]
[문이 열림]
[DOOR CREAKING]
[문이 삐걱거리는 소리]
I already told you, didn't I?
내가 이미 말했지, 그렇지?
The last time I spoke to my dad was five months ago.
지난번에 아빠랑 얘기했을 때 5개월 전이었어요.
And before that?
그리고 그 전에?
Sometimes, it's once a month.
때로는 한 달에 한 번입니다.
- [DOOR CLOSES] - We call each other.
- [문이 닫힘] - 서로 전화해요.
Sometimes, it's often.
때로는 종종 그렇습니다.
Then there are days when we don't make a call at all.
그러다가 그런 날이 있어요 우리는 전혀 전화를 걸지 않습니다.
But he hasn't gone without communication this long.
하지만 그는 없이는 가지 않았다 이렇게 오랫동안 소통해요.
That's why I'm worried.
그래서 걱정이 된다.
But the question stays the same.
그러나 질문은 동일하게 유지됩니다.
Why was Leon also looking for him?
레온은 왜 그랬지? 너도 그 사람을 찾고 있어?
Why don't you just ask your brother then?
그냥 물어보는 게 어때? 그럼 네 동생은?
[SCOFFS] Do you think I haven't asked him yet?
[비웃는다] 당신은 생각합니까 내가 아직 그 사람한테 물어보지 않았나요?
I already asked him.
나는 이미 그에게 물었습니다.
But he didn't say anything.
그러나 그는 아무 말도 하지 않았습니다.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[날카롭게 숨을 내쉰다]
You know, I think my brother already knew your father.
내 생각엔 내 동생인 것 같아 네 아버지는 이미 알고 있었어.
Why do you think so?
왜 그렇게 생각하시나요?
[JUSTIN] He wanted to know something about your father.
[저스틴] 그는 알고 싶었어요 당신 아버지에 관한 것.
That's why he's investigating.
그래서 그가 조사를 하는 거죠.
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
[불길한 음악 재생]
[JUAN] Is he investigating about the treasure?
[JUAN] 그 사람이 조사하는 건가요? 보물에 대해서?
Aside from him being the one who renovated Hotel 88,
그 사람인 것 외에도 호텔 88을 개조한 사람,
did your father have any other goals on this island?
네 아버지는 그랬어? 이 섬에 다른 목표가 있나요?
Didn't he say anything to you?
그 사람이 너한테 아무 말도 안 했어?
Nothing.
아무것도 아님.
Hm.
흠.
Maybe there's something here that can help us.
어쩌면 여기에 뭔가가 있을지도 몰라 그것은 우리에게 도움이 될 수 있습니다.
Let me handle it.
제가 처리하겠습니다.
[FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[불길한 음악이 계속됩니다]
[PHONE RINGING]
[전화벨이 울림]
I thought it would still take a while.
그럴 줄 알았는데 아직 시간이 좀 걸립니다.
But it happened now.
하지만 지금 그런 일이 일어났습니다.
[ANDY] I'm one step closer.
[앤디] 한걸음 더 가까워졌습니다.
I can finally go to places in Hotel 88 I've never been to.
드디어 갈 수 있는 곳이 있어 호텔 88에는 가본 적이 없어요.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[감동적인 음악 재생]
I may not have succeeded at first.
성공하지 못했을 수도 있다 처음에는.
But now, I will do it.
하지만 이제는 그렇게 할게요.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[서스펜스적인 음악이 계속됩니다]
You have something going on with Sir Kiko, Miss Jade.
무슨 일이 일어나고 있는 중이에요 Sir Kiko, Miss Jade와 함께
I can feel it in my fingers, and in my hair...
손가락으로 느낄 수 있어요. 그리고 내 머리에도...
in your heart!
당신의 마음속에!
[RAPHIE SQUEALING]
[래피 비명소리]
You're flirting with a guest!
당신은 손님을 유혹하고 있습니다!
I don't care if you flirt with people outside,
당신이 바람피워도 상관없어요 밖에 있는 사람들과
but don't do that inside the hotel!
하지만 그러지 마세요 호텔 내부!
What if the universe sent the wrong signs?
우주가 있다면 어떨까요? 잘못된 신호를 보냈나요?
So, you're going to run away with me?
그래서 당신은 나랑 도망갈래?
To get rid of the negative energy that's making you cry.
부정적인 것을 없애기 위해 당신을 울게 만드는 에너지.
This is what I really wanted. I just...
이것이 내가 정말로 원했던 것입니다. 난 그냥...
I just didn't think it would be this easy.
난 그냥 생각하지 않았어 이렇게 쉬울 줄이야.